hey Bose and hi soan I am Mr Bean and
zel India team asked me to narrate their
last two years journey to you because
they believed a happy and articulative
person like me will do the right
Kickstart LOL am a good buddy for you
all zeld Dy mess migration zel pass
defects closure zel flexible messaging
zel fraud SLS scam education ews
compliance epics zel activity redesign
limits simplification and zel being the
highle deliverables there is a long
journey filled with achievements success
challenges sweat and blood 2023 was a
roller coaster ride in a time frame of
just 7 months we completed two important
modules of deeps payment party and
transaction order 337 PS defects are
brought down to 30 in a time frame of 2
years we feel accomplished because for
activity redesign success uccessful
launch 90% of the work is done from zel
7 8 and nine teams with around 2290 plus
story points and delivered it with zero
defects this involved M2 Ops DB changes
without a DBA from India we did that
role while us scrums had DBA do it for
them for other upcs we successfully
tested it for iOS Android and desktop
with no testers available relied on our
bdd Automation and and some portions of
manual testing by our developers for
stored procedure related changes there
were dedicated teams for our us friends
but we died into SP and started finding
bugs which helped us move a defect free
code to
production we feel accomplished because
for zelog right from ideation to
implementation everything is driven from
India teens while other teams are
confined to their components zel 78 and
nine picked up M2 changes Ops changes
reverse sync customer profile payment
party transaction order processor
changes and end-to-end testing as well
surprised all us product and Tech
Partners in the record time this has
been completed with literally zero
dependency on any of the US Partners
proactively found the edge cases and
aligned product to include it in the
road maps exhibiting our domain
expertise we feel accomplished because
DPS we are the first ones to get on
board to Orchestra many performance
Improvement activities initiated and
done by India DP Ms team endtoend
testing manual done by our teens first
team to write bdds in karate framework
over 33 million customers live with
deeps multiple relevant dashboards
created that eased monitoring of
migration while this is all success and
accomplishments lot more to come on
challenges and the journey now team will
spe
let me sign off thank you